# Anton Schur

**(a)** 1ast | **iii** Anton Schur | **②** LastStranger | **№** schur2982@gmail.com | **1** +375(33)380-11-79

#### Summary

As an Android developer with three years of experience, I have in-depth knowledge of the Android platform and proficiency in Java and Kotlin. I have experience working with tools such as Android Studio, Gradle, and ProGuard. Also, I worked with NFC, GPIO, and encryption, wrote complex algorithms for user location, and implemented best practices in software development, including design patterns and RESTful API principles. I want to obtain a position in professional development where my skills and knowledge are valued and can benefit the organization.

# Work Experience

Android Developer June 2024 - Present

Kate Media

- Added new features to project, to match customer requirements;
- Updated project to newest technologies, build time has been reduced by almost two times;
- Fully covered 30 modules and 10 support libraries of app with tests;
- Rewrote a lot of API's on project, that fixed some old bugs and reduced development time;

Android Developer May 2023 - May 2024

Heads & Hands

- Successfully prepared 3 apps for publishing in Google Play;
- Adopted code for multi-app builds (2 apps in one code base);
- In cooperation with BE team refactored telemetry remote API in the app, which reduced analytic network calls by 30%;
- Optimised one of the most heavily loaded parts of the application, that fully removes freezing from app.

Android Developer Nov 2021 - June 2024

Science Solutions

- Single-handedly wrote and handed over to the customer app that works with NFC, QR-reading, and custom encryption without documentation;
- Realised custom complex algorithm that shows ads depending on location;
- Wrote custom player that can show content depending on its type (Text, image, or video);
- Optimised processes on the team, reducing decision time by 50%.

#### Projects

KateMedia June 2024 - Present

KateMedia is a product company, that specialize at restaurant business.

#### KateTablet

KateTablet is product to automate processes in restaurants. It provides opportunities to order, pay and entertain without server. As a developer on this project, I fully covered project, modules and support libraries with tests. Also, I added new features to project. I refactored part of internal API's, that removed old bugs and added new functionality. I updated all project libraries, to match Google requirements.

Heads and Hands May 2023 - May 2024

Heads and Hands is a large outsource company, that specialize at e-commerce.

Funday

Funday - app for online shopping in a big chain of clothing stores. As a developer on this project, I implemented the Profile page and its subpages, product listing, category pages, and parts of ordering. Also, I changed user analytics and telemetry in the app, which reduced network calls, app size, and app loading on the system. I refactored part of the code, that optimized UI and user input and removed any freezing in the app.

Link to App

Science Solutions November 2021 - June 2024

Science solutions is a mixed company, that has it own product and outsource direction

PVIS

Passengers visual information system - service for displaying ads and useful information in public transport. As a Project Lead, I defined and created the app's architecture. Also, I wrote the most complex algorithms that use the location of transport to show ads, and GPIO integration without any documentation for device, admin, root rights, and player, which can show a lot of custom content (not only video). Also, I wrote all the design, network, and database layers of the app and its main logic.

#### Controller app

Controller app - service for public transport controllers, that work with NFC, QR scanning, custom encryption, and custom complex location algorithm. This app uses a lot of custom technologies, but it can be started and worked on any phone with NFC and a camera. In this app, all custom technologies integration, network, database layer, UI, domain logic, and algorithms were realized by myself.

# **EDUCATION**

2018 - 2022 Bachelor's Degree at Belarusian State University of Informatics and Radio-electronics, AI faculty

## SKILLS

Kotlin, Java, SQL, Android SDK, KMP, MV\* Architecture, Jetpack libs, Compose Multiplatform, Material Design (2, 3), Koin, Dagger Hilt, Coroutines, Rest API, Ktor, Retrofit2, Okhttp3, Room, SharedPreferances, DataStore, LiveData, Flow, Cicerone, Navigation Component, Glide, Picasso, Coil, Lottie, Firebase, AppMetrica, Notion, AppsFlyer, JUnit, Mockito, Espresso.

### LANGUAGES

English B1 Russian Native